Ali Afarinifard

Zanjan, Iran

0098-993-149-8394

Linkedin | Github | aliafarinifard@outlook.com | aliafarinifard.liara.run

SUMMARY

I'm a passionate and young Software Engineer packing **more than 3+ years** of hands-on experience as a front end developer. Yet willing to work **Hybrid** or **Remote** with backend technologies as well to expand my current skill set. I'm Looking for a challenging environment where I can prove my ability to solve complex problems and bring value to both the customers and the business.

SKILLS

JavaScript | TypeScript | Next JS | React JS | Redux | HTML | CSS | SASS | Tailwind | MUI

EXPERIENCE

Asia Startup

Tehran - Iran

Front End Developer

October 2023 - January 2024

- Planned, developed, tested, and maintained responsive websites and web applications.
- Working with TypeScript, Material UI (MUI), Ant Design, TailwindCSS, REST api.
- Implemented Medical E-Commerce Dashboard Panel with React.
- Implemented Medical website with Next.js.
- Built reusable components that used in all projects.

Freelancer

Front End Developer

august 2020 - present

- Developing, optimizing and maintaining the websites and applications with Next JS, React JS, Typescript to meet my clients needs and goals.
- build a web application from start to finish.

EDUCATION

B.Sc Computer Software Engineer – Qazvin Islamic Azad University Qazvin - Iran | September 2020 - July 2023